{
    "id": "62c778f5509f497bbec38258d4c94789",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Why are you always cutting .................................... on my conversations?",
            "description": "To cut in is to interrupt someone who is speaking.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "472638bc42784551b60eb58666b9584c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hamlet is cut ................................... from the other human settlements in the area.",
            "description": "If something is cut off, it cannot be accessed easily.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "715633566e2140488b43c97a85b1c059"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her relationship with her family is falling ....................................",
            "description": "To fall apart is to break into parts.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "apart",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1221f7ea98947cca49539c8b3a5a291"
        },
        {
            "question": "If his career in the show business does not take off, he always has his professional degrees to fall ......................................",
            "description": "To fall back on something is to use it when nothing else works.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "on",
                "back on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "10a387e2c11045039bf0d43b733ad454"
        },
        {
            "question": "We drove home to get ................................... from the crowd.",
            "description": "To get away is to escape a place.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45edc2c6c8ff4edebd177290a5ca34cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took her quite some time to get .......................................... her loss.",
            "description": "To get over something is to stop feeling bad about something terrible that has happened in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5736c13ebdc49f093a4c8d8b9ff62f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The newly opened restaurant is giving ......................................... free coupons.",
            "description": "To give away is to distribute.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a2a84c1f42a34367b1973d838b410c0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The task was so arduous that I gave .......................................... fairly quickly.",
            "description": "To give up is to stop trying.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ebde333d72dd4db0a889223b11827793"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was so excited when he invited me to go .......................................... with him.",
            "description": "To go out with somebody is to have a romantic date with them.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5feab3dd7d743e1b38dc1e132ce24e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She held ........................................ her disappointment.",
            "description": "To hold back your feelings is to hide them.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "off",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01338b29cbdc4ee282615b9dfcd2094a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Go .....................................! Nothing will stop you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "ahead",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bbd22b8470b74e6a91c7effc1ce5eaa1"
        },
        {
            "question": "A good owner must be able to call ......................................... their dog.",
            "description": "To call off a dog is to stop the animals from behaving aggressively.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aa0582ec96ca4e45841e0964b82e686b"
        }
    ]
}